<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <MCS.repairsequesttitle>Repairs request</MCS.repairsequesttitle>
  <MCS.repairsequest>-- Comlink with MiningCo. --

MiningCo. pilot:

"Hello partner!
Our ship is damaged and we need some repairs before going back to the orbital station.
Help us and we will reward you. Business as usual!

-- End of transmission --

WARNING! Not helping the ship will negatively impact your partnership with MiningCo..</MCS.repairsequest>
  <MCS.repairscompletetitle>Repairs completed</MCS.repairscompletetitle>
  <MCS.repairscomplete>-- Comlink with MiningCo. --

MiningCo. pilot:

"We are really grateful for your help, partner!
Tonight, we will drink to your colony in the orbital ship mess.
Here, take those crates as a compensation for your efforts. You have well earned it.

See you soon partner!"

-- End of transmission --</MCS.repairscomplete>
  <MCS.repairscompletesosotitle>Partial repairs</MCS.repairscompletesosotitle>
  <MCS.repairscompletesoso>-- Comlink with MiningCo. --

MiningCo. pilot:

"We are grateful for your help, partner!
This is not perfect but at least, you tried.
Here, take those crates as a compensation for your efforts.

See you partner!"

-- End of transmission --</MCS.repairscompletesoso>
  <MCS.repairscompletebadtitle>Failed repairs</MCS.repairscompletebadtitle>
  <MCS.repairscompletebad>-- Comlink with MiningCo. --

MiningCo. pilot:

"Well, it seems the repairs did not go as we expected.
You have supplied us the materials but our ship is in worse condition than when we landed.
You should really review the MiningCo. spaceship maintenance manual!

See you partner!"

-- End of transmission --</MCS.repairscompletebad>
  <MCS.repairscompletenonetitle>Repairs?!</MCS.repairscompletenonetitle>
  <MCS.repairscompletenone>-- Comlink with MiningCo. --

MiningCo. pilot:

"Well, it seems you cannot help us. Headquarters will not be pleased to hear that.
MiningCo. does not bother making business with weak partners.

Do not count on our services for some time, "partner"."

-- End of transmission --

Next cargo supply is delayed.
Airstrike is not available for some time.</MCS.repairscompletenone>
  <MCS.repairscompleteworsttitle>Repairs?!</MCS.repairscompleteworsttitle>
  <MCS.repairscompleteworst>-- Comlink with MiningCo. --

MiningCo. pilot:

"I can't believe it! Our ship is in worse condition than when we landed.
I am not supplying this rathole any soon!"

(You can hear insults before the pilot disconnects.)

-- End of transmission --

Next cargo supply is greatly delayed.
Airstrike is not available for a long time.</MCS.repairscompleteworst>
  <MCS.damagedmedictitle>Medical spaceship damaged</MCS.damagedmedictitle>
  <MCS.damagedmedic>-- Comlink with MiningCo. --
  
"Our medical spaceship was damaged during the last supply.
Repairs will take some times.

Remember the MiningCo. partnership contract stipulates that you must ensure landing ships security!"

-- End of transmission --</MCS.damagedmedic>
  <MCS.damagedcargotitle>Cargo spaceship damaged</MCS.damagedcargotitle>
  <MCS.damagedcargo>-- Comlink with MiningCo. --

"Our cargo spaceship was damaged during the last supply.
Repairs will take some times.

Remember the MiningCo. partnership contract stipulates that you must ensure landing ships security!\"

-- End of transmission --</MCS.damagedcargo>
  <MCS.lostshiptitle>Spaceship destroyed</MCS.lostshiptitle>
  <MCS.lostship>-- Comlink with MiningCo. --
  
"We just lost contact with one of our ships in your sector.
Whatever happened, you are held responsible of this loss.

Pay a compensation or say goodbye to our partnership!"

-- End of transmission --</MCS.lostship>
  <MCS.medicinjuredtitle>Medic down</MCS.medicinjuredtitle>
  <MCS.medicinjured>A MiningCo. medic has been downed or killed while helping your colony.

Medics are precious people, even more on rimworlds. Losing one will obviously anger MiningCo. and nobody wants to anger this company.
Remember that you must ensure their safety in your area!</MCS.medicinjured>
  <MCS.keeppawntitle>Orbital "guests"</MCS.keeppawntitle>
  <MCS.keeppawninfo>-- Comlink with MiningCo. --

"A friend of yours is being healed in our medibay. I think we will keep {0} aboard as... "guest" for {1} own safety.
It is really dangerous down there, you know, and there are lot of menial - ehr, I mean "interresting" - tasks to do aboard an orbital station to keep {0} occupied.

MiningCo. medibay officer out."

-- End of transmission --

The following colonist is kept as "guest" aboard the orbital station until you pay a compensation: {2}.</MCS.keeppawninfo>
  <MCS.keeppawn>-- Comlink with MiningCo. --
"Some friends of yours are being healed in our medibay. I think we will keep them aboard as... "guests" for their own safety.
It is really dangerous down there, you know, and there are lot of menial - ehr, I mean "interresting" - tasks to do aboard an orbital station to keep them occupied.

MiningCo. medibay officer out."

-- End of transmission --

The following colonists are kept as "guests" aboard the orbital station until you pay a compensation: </MCS.keeppawn>
  <MCS.healingdonetitle>Orbital healing finished</MCS.healingdonetitle>
  <MCS.healingdone>-- Comlink with MiningCo. --

"Healing of {0} is now finished. Everything went fine during the treatment.
We just launched {1} drop pod toward your colony.

I hope you are satisfied of our services.

MiningCo. medibay officer out."

-- End of transmission --</MCS.healingdone>
  <MCS.healingfailtitle>Orbital healing interrupted</MCS.healingfailtitle>
  <MCS.healingfail>-- Comlink with MiningCo. --
"Though we did our best to heal {0}, it seems {1} metabolism was disturbed by the last injection.

I am afraid that we need to immediately send {2} back to you as our rules strictly forbid civilian body storage.

Please accept these silvers as a compensation.

MiningCo. medibay officer out."

-- End of transmission --</MCS.healingfail>
</LanguageData>
